Are you all right!?
Hang in there!
PUNCH
LINE!
rain!
pa-pantyshot, pu-punchline
chi
ra
peek
rain!
pa-pantyshot, pu-punchline
chi
ra
peek
rain!
pa-pantyshot, pu-punchline
chi
ra
peek
rain!
pa-pantyshot, pu-punchline
chi
ra
peek
Twenty five centimeters above the knee,
PUNCH
LINE!
ki
se
tsu
kan
What?
just not giving a damn about the seasons
PUNCH
LINE!
For a girl, the length of the skirt
is inversely proportional to her feelings
I beg your pardon?
Please refrain from such uncouth words
There's nothing indecent about it
Girls are allowed
to wear whatever they want
Even flustering and fumbling around,
cret
Heart
nan
de
I still can't let you peek into my secret heart
nan
de!?
Why?
Love
You
Why can't I just say that I love you?
My heart of hearts
is overflowing with these hot, hot feelings
Yes! Yes! I want to give it to you!
YES!
It's over.
Campanella Kick!
Miyazawa Kenji has arrived!
You!
How...
I happen to be clairvoyant.
Nor losing to bullets
If that's the case,
you should know I still have bullets.
The hero of justice,
Strange Juice, is on the scene!
So, now what?
It's two against one!
I see how it is.
I'll have to show you my true power.
That's...
It can't be.
Oh, but it can.
I too am Über, just like the two of you.
Except my powers exceed yours by nearly 2,000 percent.
You understand what that means, don't you?
Who cares!?
Bastard!
What is your goal?
I guess you could say I'm in pursuit of an ideal world.
To find it, I must rid it of inferior humans
so that the superior W can rule the world.
W?
St—
Stop!
Move.
Stop.
Please.
You're in the way.
Die.
Stop it!
I can't let you go on like this any longer!
But why now!?
I'm simply trying to fulfill your wish!
But you can't!
Not Ito!
Please.
Lend me your strength.
You.
I'm talking to you, Yuuta!
You can see me?
Just use this, quickly!
Cinnamon...
Shit, my power! My power!
Now!
Wh-What? What!?
P-Panties!
Impossible...
How?
How are you able to become Über?
Shut up!
I didn't ask to become this way!
Huh?
Why am I...
Meika!
Meika! Meika!
Please, wake up!
Meika!
What are you crying about, Rabura?
Muhi!
Now then, let's have a look at your face.
No way...
You know him, Ito?
Tomoda Chihaya.
He's my homeroom teacher.
Why would a teacher do something like this?
I did all this because I love you, Ito.
What are you saying?
It's because I loved you that I edited the video
and sent out the emails.
Then the person who killed Meiko and Moena...
I was possessed by the ghost of the
Qmay Group's leader, Tsubouchi Qmei.
He's the one who killed them.
What's going on?
I made a contract with Tsubouchi's spirit.
In exchange for the use of my body, he promised to grant me a wish.
A wish?
Revenge.
I knew...
I knew that Ito was being harassed at school.
I couldn't forgive them.
We were destined to be together, Ito.
And your classmates were just getting in our way.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to hide it.
I know you love me, too.
If our love was to be, I had to punish them.
That's a true test of love, right?
Isn't it?
This guy gives me the heebie-jeebies.
Does that mean you've still got that Tsubouchi guy inside you?
My body's useless to him as it is now.
Because of the Überification.
You know what that is?
More accurately, it's Übermenschification.
Once infected with the so-called Hercules virus,
hosts undergo an epigenetic process that toggles genetic switches.
It changes their bodily composition,
allowing them to exert power beyond their normal limits.
They can't do it all of the time, though.
Even those infected normally have limiters.
However, those can be removed. And when they do...
They become Über.
Exactly.
But becoming Über comes with great risks.
Doing it over and over
causes severe damage and atrophy to the body.
And then...
...you die.
That's what happened to Tsubouchi, as well.
That bear cub was the key to
allowing his body to regenerate.
That's why it was made.
Using that bear's extraordinary regenerative capacity,
he could've evaded death while becoming Über regularly.
You disgust me.
Even now, you're being dishonest to yourself.
Listen, I have one last wish.
Ito,
don't die.
Survive.
That's my—
You piece of shit!
Ito!
You're just a perverted teacher!
How dare you even think selfish crap like that!?
Stop!
Possessed by a ghost, my ass!
You seriously piss me off!
The Next Day
It's New Year's Eve! Meika-emon
And... why are we having swimming soba?
It's New Year's Eve. Soba is a tradition.
I get the soba part, but why swimming?
It's totally off-season.
What do you think Ito?
Whatever.
It's New Year's Eve! Meika-emon
Why are you being such a party pooper?
Meika, can I speak to you in private?
So you're sure it's all right?
What's all right?
You know, the servers.
At AFSPC.
I told you, I hacked into the U.S. military's servers,
but everything was normal.
Well, okay...
Besides, if there were any chance of an asteroid collision,
the whole world would be freaking out right now.
It's New Year's Eve. Let's go back to Meika-emon's party
and bring down the roof!
Okay?
It's New Year's Eve, Meika-emon
Sushi rice, sushi rice, chirashi sushi,
I'll wait for you,
Kuzushi...
Not your best.
It's New Year's Eve! Meika-emon
But it's for our upcoming musical!
It's just lacking in girlish sentiment.
Have you ever been in love, Mikatan?
In love?
I guess I haven't met anyone.
Yes, you have.
There's one person, isn't there?
Oh, yeah, there's Yuuta!
Why don't you try falling in love with him?
Look at her face!
She already has!
I-It's not like that!
He's a she, though.
It's New Year's Eve! Meika-emon
You're kidding, right?
Biologically, she's unmistakably female.
I've kept it a secret until now because it's a delicate issue.
Iridatsu Yu
The truth is her registered legal name is Iridatsu Yuu.
"Yuuta" is just a name she gave herself.
S-Speaking of, where is Yuuta?
It's New Year's Eve! Meika-emon
I invited her, but...
It's up to you, then.
Hey, so what else have you been hiding from us?
About Iridatsu?
That too, but...
Tell me about your and Mikatan's past.
All right.
Just a little, then.
It was eight years ago that I first met Narugino.
It was a summer night...
What a stormy, summer night it was.
Quit yer cryin'!
Who are you?
I'm Daihatsu Meika.
I've come to shelter, raise and support you.
Oh, and I'm a robot.
So why did the apartment burn down?
Narugino escaped from a research facility with the help of someone named Ishigata.
But it wasn't long before they were discovered.
So Ishigata went out in a blaze of glory,
taking their pursuers with him.
I decided it was best to flee Tokyo with Narugino.
We went far, far to the north.
Eventually we settled down
in the foothills of the mountains of Aomori.
We rented a rundown shack and made a life for ourselves there.
It's over. I'm superior.
From that point on, I trained my pupil.
Day after day after day, we trained
in order to draw out her inner strength.
It wasn't until after she had turned 13, however, that the seed we had nurtured sprang to life.
You'll pay...
You'll pay!
Ever since then, she's been in the business of kicking ass everywhere she goes,
taking out the bad guys one by one.
The people of Tsugaru saw Narugino, and called her...
Pantyhose Girl
The Hero of Tsugaru
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
The Hero of Tsugaru
Pantyhose Girl
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The Hero of Tsugaru
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The Hero of Tsugaru
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The Hero of Tsugaru
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
The Hero of Tsugaru
Pantyhose Girl
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The Hero of Tsugaru
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
The Hero of Tsugaru
Pantyhose Girl
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The Hero of Tsugaru
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The Hero of Tsugaru
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
The Hero of Tsugaru
Pantyhose Girl
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
The Hero of Tsugaru
Pantyhose Girl
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
Pantyhose Girl
The Hero of Tsugaru
The fists of justice
clobbers another!
"Pantyhose Girl"!? No way!
DDY saves fansubbing!
We can't help that.
It's to protect your identity.
That's why I didn't want to become a hero!
My dream is to become an idol!
Give up on that dream.
You have to become a hero,
or we can't form the secret
crime-fighting force, Justice Punch.
That name's so lame. I hate it.
What do you want to call it, then?
Like, Pretty Cutie Moon—
Too long! And you're ripping off a bunch of things!
In any case, you were born to become a hero.
That's your destiny.
You can't get away from it.
Destiny?
What's this?
Your new costume.
Starting today, you're Strange Juice.
You're going to fight evil as a new hero...
in Tokyo!
So that's why you came to Korai House?
But now, we're thinking it's time to bring this hero story to an end.
Huh?
Isn't it obvious?
Narugino has gone Über too many times.
Has her body...
I don't know how I missed it.
After all the time we've spent together...
It's New Year's Eve! Meika-emon
Yuuta-kun wasn't home.
I think he's out somewhere.
Well, then.
Let's get started, shall we?
With what?
Meika, we're out of fireworks.
Fret not!
I've kept a bottle rocket for just such a special occasion.
A special occasion?
I've never seen it around.
Just come with me.
Mikatan?
Oh, I just remembered I have something to do.
Go ahead without me.
Really?
Okay, well come down when you're done.
No way!
I forgot to refill my medicine.
Narugino!
I've got to tell someone!
Miyazawa Kenji?
Wh-What is this?
I call it the Kaku-maker!
Kaku-maker
(Revolution maker)
Uh, where's the bottle rocket?
There!
See it up there?
What's the matter today, Miyako-chan?
Sensei, I—
We interrupt this program to deliver breaking news.
Asteroid VR-1, which was thought not to be on a collision path with Earth,
Two kilometer diameter asteroid
strike imminent
will... collide...
Will imminently collide with Earth.
I repeat, Asteroid VR-1's collision is imminent.
Well, it couldn't be helped.
Unbeijini nyopurasara,
I'm going to put a spell on you.
Unbeijini nyopurakura,
I'm going to protect...
That song...
How...
Mikatan, what's keeping you?
Now, go!
Hurry up!
Your friends are calling.
But—
Just go!
Hurry up, or else I'm going to launch the rocket without you!
I promise to listen to you more later.
A promise for later, huh?
You're there, aren't you?
Come down here.
What's your deal!?
How can you see me?
How is that possible?
Meika said everything was normal on the AFSPC servers!
And the Qmay Group hasn't finished
preparations for their W-ruled world.
You'll know the answer once you have your body back.
I need some book called the Nandala Gandala for tha—
You mean this?
Nandala Gandala
Are you messing with me!?
You could have made a better fake than this!
Just look inside.
I did!
It's all blank, with just one word!
What the hell is a U-turn?
Just as it says.
No, what does it mean—
Are you telling me to go back in time?
If I were, when would you go back to?
To before everything began...
December 21st.
That alone isn't enough to take you back in time.
There's one other thing you need.
A strong desire to save someone.
I don't need to tell you the rest.
Yuuta, history is about to make a huge mistake.
It's a future that cannot be allowed to happen.
Change history.
I failed in my mission.
Many of us have attempted it and made the same mistakes.
Nevertheless, I leave my hopes with you.
No. All of our hopes.
Why?
Yuuta, wish for it.
Wish hard, from the bottom of your heart.
That desire will grant you power.
You're going to change destiny.
Change history!
Yuuta!
I'll do it.
I'll change history.
For Meika, I'll do it.
For Rabura, I'll do it.
For Ito, I'll do it.
For Narugino, I'll do it.
I'm going to protect them.
I promise. I promise. I promise!
I'm counting on you, me.
The asteroid
hits.
Humanity falls.
nee monitaa no naka no sekai ja utsuranai
The world behind a screen couldn't possibly display
kimi e no omoi
my love for you
aa miesou de mienai haato no shigunaru
Though I can't quite see the signals from your heart,
namiutsu koi moyou
I can almost feel the waveforms of love
nandomo chikazuite tsugi koso wa no kurikaeshi
Every time we come close, I decide I'll say it next time
kakushiteru hohoemi tashikametai
I want to be sure that your hidden smiles are for me
tokimeki o kakiatsume kimi no te o nigirishime
My heart is pounding as I clutch your hand in mine
kagi kaketa sono kokoro aketemiseru yo
You'll see that I can open the lock to your heart
konnanimo kimi ga suki de tamaranai
I can't contain my feelings for you any more
kono koe wo todoketainda
I just want my voice to reach you
Honey Honey tte sakebu emooshon
so I'll shout "Honey, Honey" with all the emotion I've got
dare yorimo kimi ga suki de tamaranai
I love you more than anyone, I can't hold it in any more
ato sukoshi kimi made no kyori
I'm so close to reaching you now
Honey Honey tte sakebu emooshon
so I'll shout "Honey, Honey" with all the emotion I've got